Guide to the Office of Community Relations, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Office of Community Relations, Yale University, records
1976-1990
RU 184
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
12.5
The records consist of subject files documenting the activities of the Office of Community Relations.
Yale University. Office of the Secretary
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 4-D (YRG 4-D), Records documenting community relations of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of subject files documenting the activities of the Office of Community Relations.
Community and college; Universities and colleges -- Administration; University towns; New Haven (Conn.); Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Public relations; Yale University. Office of Community Relations; Yale University. Office of the Secretary
- Administrative records, 1976-1990; Accession 1995-A-071
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2025
  - Directory of Programs, Nale-New Haven Public School, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Democracy in New Haven, Kutz, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - President's Reception for DeLieto, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - H.O.M.E. Inc., New Haven, 1989 February (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Hospitality - New Haven a New Attitude, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Homeless Shelter NH, 1988 May 9 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Hartford Student -Reception, 1989 February 23 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Girl Scouts 75th Anniversary, 1987 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anne Frank, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ed Fischer Memorial, 1988 December 4 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Downtown Evening Soup Kitchen Event, 1988 September 22 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ethics Commission, 1989 August 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Earth Day, 1990 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NAACP Youth Council, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Arts Festival, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut Celebration 350 plus pre-party reception, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - City Recycling, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Proposed Community Breakfasts, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Proposal for NH city Employees to take Yale Courses, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - P.I.L.O.T., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Lobbying for P.I.L.O.T., 1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Lobbying for P.I.L.O.T., 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Lobbying for P.I.L.O.T., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Women in Leadership, 1989 May 12 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - West Haven Information, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - West Haven Taxes, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Urban League, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Urban League Dinner, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Urban League Job Fair, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Urban League Dinner, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Bob Doss (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - University of Connecticut (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Travel Host Magazines (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - More Travel Host Magazines (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Toys for Tots, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Dinner for Lloyd Richards, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Revenue Commission, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Revenue Commission, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - YMCA Fire plus additional YMCA Information, 1989 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Peabody Museum (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Other Universities Info, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Community Mairs Conference, 1984 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Lagoon Bathhouse, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Hosts - John Bhoreyeb Assoc, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - New Haven Revenue Commission (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - New Haven Police Emerald Society (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - New Haven Building Fire Codes (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Natl Resource Survey (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - NH Parks, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - NAACP - Dinner, 1989 May 25 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Conn Conf of Independent Colleges (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Legislative Session, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - The Learning Center, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Leadership Greater NH, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - New Haven Public Schook, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Helping Hands Dinner, 1989 April 26 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Dixwell-Newhallville (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Neighborhood Corp, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Dixwell Property, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Dixwell Training Programs, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Dixwell Q House (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Brown Bag Forum (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - L.U.L. A.C. (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - League of United Latin American (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Citizens (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Lighthouse Park Carousel (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Dwight Neighborhood Area (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Revitalization Program, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - NH Pilot commission, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - NH Sister Cities (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - NH Open Tennis Tournament, 89 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Democracy in NH: A History of the Board of Alderman, 1638-1988 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - New Haven Peace Center (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Urban League, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Radioactive Waste (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Saybrook Ct 350 Anniversary (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Poverty Commission Rpt, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - NH 350th Anniversary (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Upper Chapel Neighborhood (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - NH 350th Lunch Series (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Our Children Our Future, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Amistad f nformation (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Amistad Meditations in Passage (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Afro-American 20th Anniversary (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Celebration, 1989 April 14-16 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - The Honorable Jonathan Pelto (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Amistad Banquet, 1989 November 9 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Alderman, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Amistad - Symposium (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Advocate, 1989 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Article Addicted By Yale (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Amistad Mailing Lists (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Amistad Press Conferences and Releases (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - The Amistad Event (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Stationary, Logos, Photos (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Yale Club Amistad Event (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Amistad Committee (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Amistad Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - New Haven Info - Yale Edition (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Cornell Study, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Construction Complaint, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - U.S. Constitution, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Bicentennial Yale Events (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - CONNPEP, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Computer Project - New Haven Schools, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Brochures - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Community and University (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Civil Defense - New Haven (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Independent School, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Public Relations Strategies, 1984 June 5 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - DiLieto Inaguration, 1905 June 8 (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Mayor's News Releases (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Mayor Ben DiLieto (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - DiLieto Commendations (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - D.A.T.A. Conference (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - 1988 Sep 29 (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Database New Haven, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Sewer Use Charges, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - Mayors' Portraits, 1984 September 26 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - New Haven Colony Historical Society (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - N.H. Water Pollution Control Authority, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - City Litter, trash, and kiosks (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - City Approvals Commission (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - City Streets (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - City Spirit Artists (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - Chamber meeting, 1989 April 26 (Box 3, Folder 128)
  - Conn Association for United (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - Spanish Action, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 130)
  - Campus Compact, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 131)
  - Apartheid Issues (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Affirmative Action Employment, 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Afro-American Cultural Center, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Conference on Aging, 1986 June 3 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - AIDS Project New Haven (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Alderman Election, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Alderman Newsclippings (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Alderman Elections (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Question Referendum, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Board of Alderman (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Board of Alderman General (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Alderman Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Amistad Symposium Lectures (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Art Gallery Symposiun (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Battered Women's Shelter (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - New Haven Bed Race, 1983 September 10 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Boston Plan (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Bowl Policy, 1981-1985 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Insurance Case, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Concerts at the Bowl (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Yale Bowl, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Yale Bowl Charity Day (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - Yale Bowl Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 155)
  - Breakfast Meetings, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 156)
  - British Art Center (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - Buchman, Christina (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - Community Affairs- other (Box 4, Folder 159)
  - Universities (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - Buckley Amendment (Box 4, Folder 161)
  - National Business Education Week (Box 4, Folder 162)
  - New Haven Bus Tour (Box 4, Folder 163)
  - Downtown Cultural Events Committee (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Downtown Developer Steering Committee (Box 5, Folder 165)
  - Downtown Transportation (Box 5, Folder 166)
  - Election, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 167)
  - Elm-Ivy Award, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 168)
  - Duke Ellington Fellowship (Box 5, Folder 169)
  - Elm Haven (Box 5, Folder 170)
  - Endowment (Box 5, Folder 171)
  - Environmental Conference (Box 5, Folder 172)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Film Societies (Box 5, Folder 174)
  - Food Drive (Box 5, Folder 175)
  - Freedom of Expression (Box 5, Folder 176)
  - Freshman Orientation (Box 5, Folder 177)
  - A. Bartlett Giamatti (Box 5, Folder 178)
  - Golf Course (Box 5, Folder 179)
  - Golf Course Zoning Building Permit (Box 5, Folder 180)
  - Green Party, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 181)
  - Grounds Maintenance (Box 5, Folder 182)
  - Hill Development Corporation (Box 5, Folder 183)
  - Development New Haven History (Box 5, Folder 184)
  - General f dormation Yale (Box 5, Folder 185)
  - Homeless (Box 5, Folder 186)
  - Housing New Haven (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Housing Married Students (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Infoline (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Infant Mortality (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Course Credit Pros (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Yale-New Haven Hospital (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Student Liaisons (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Marketing New Haven (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Applications and Approvals (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Calendar of Events (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - Center for the City, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Chapel Haven (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Community Labor Alliance (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Community Relations, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Community Soup Kitchen (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Conference Services (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Visitors Info Downtown Council, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Corporation Info (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Cultural Affairs- Marketing Yask Force (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - Cultural Affairs (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Day Care (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Day Carel Parents Co-op (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Development Projects (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - DeVane Lecture Invitations (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Divinity School (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - Dixwell Avenue (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Dixwell House (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - Yale Charities (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Alumni and Yale/New Haven Relations (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Community Action Agency (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Community Conversations (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - Computer Center, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - Computer Network Project (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Conference Ofice (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - CHEA (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - State Commissioners (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - CONNECTIONS-, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 223)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 224)
  - Traffic Study, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 225)
  - Logue Report, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - LoRicco Bldg (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - March of Dimes (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - New Haven (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - New Haven Green (Box 6, Folder 230)
  - New Haven 350 Celebration (Box 6, Folder 231)
  - New Haven Public Schools, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 232)
  - NH Neighborhoods (Box 6, Folder 233)
  - The Palace (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Parking (Box 6, Folder 235)
  - Parking Lots (Box 6, Folder 236)
  - Parking #71 (Box 6, Folder 237)
  - PILOT (Box 6, Folder 238)
  - PILOT, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - PILOT, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - PILOT, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - PILOT, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - PLOT, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Pilot Expansion (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Court Decision, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Yale Press, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - YPI History (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - YPI Approvals (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Cedarhurst School (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Conference - Positive Youth (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - Development, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Public Relations, 1982-193 (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Public Relations, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Red Cross (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Research at Yale (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Rideshare Downtown Parking (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Benno Schmidt, Jr. (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Schiavone (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Science Park Agreements (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Science Park Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Science Park Published Materials (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Science Park Press Releases (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Substance Abuse (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Mayor John Daniels (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Symposium, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Symposium, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Symposium, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Tax Exempt Worksheets (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Taxable Property- Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Taxable Property (Box 8, Folder 270)
  - Tax Exempt Property- Legal News (Box 8, Folder 271)
  - Exempt Property (Box 8, Folder 272)
  - Tax Tssues- David Warren file (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Tax Exemption Challenges-, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Tax Issued Cornell Study, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Tax Issues- Harvard (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Tax Issues - Other Universities (Box 8, Folder 277)
  - Tax Comparison (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Community Relations- Other Colleges (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - FIH Report (Box 8, Folder 280)
  - Underground Utilities (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Union (Box 8, Folder 282)
  - Union Negotiations (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - VoIunteer Services (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Other Colleges- Work Study (Box 8, Folder 285)
  - Work-Study (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Yale-New Haven Hospital (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Y.P.I. Plan (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Sheila Wellington (Box 9)
  - SWW staff meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
  - SWW tasks (Box 9)
  - Office of the Secretary, transition (Box 9)
  - Connections- A Community Guide to Yale (Box 10)
  - Hillhouse historic district, 1985 (Box 10)
  - Summer and Special programs, -1978 (Box 10)
  - Annual report (community relations), 1987 (Box 10)
  - Elm Street nomination maps (Box 10)
  - Historic districts-general (Box 10)
  - New Haven Preservation Trust (Box 10)
  - Historic property (Box 10)
  - IRS (Box 10)
  - Legislature plans, 1988 (Box 10)
  - New Haven information (Box 10)
  - Community Relations correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence with Benno Schmidt (Box 10)